{
    "subject": "resource/Chanak_Crisis",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:1922_in_France",
    "human_readable": "The Chanak Crisis is about 1922 in France.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7351992726325989,
            "question": "How did the Chanak Crisis impact France?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.596776008605957,
            "question": "Is the Chanak Crisis a historical event?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5928811430931091,
            "question": "When did the Chanak Crisis occur?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5494486093521118,
            "question": "What year is associated with the Chanak Crisis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5205177068710327,
            "question": "What was the outcome of the Chanak Crisis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4694197475910187,
            "question": "Where did the Chanak Crisis take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3445253372192383,
            "question": "What were the main causes of the Chanak Crisis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3363243341445923,
            "question": "Are there any lasting consequences from the Chanak Crisis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3207548260688782,
            "question": "Were there any international implications of the Chanak Crisis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2827153503894806,
            "question": "Who were the key players involved in the Chanak Crisis?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Chanak Crisis is about 1922 in France.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3007_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any international implications of the Chanak Crisis?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3007_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any lasting consequences from the Chanak Crisis?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3007_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were the main causes of the Chanak Crisis?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3007_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3007_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3007_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3007_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3007_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3007_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3007_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3007_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3007_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3007_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3007_68.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\nThe provided text states that the Chanak Crisis occurred in **1922** between the United Kingdom and Turkey, not France. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that none of the documents mention a connection between the Chanak Crisis and France. In fact, most documents mention the crisis as occurring between the United Kingdom and Turkey, with some mentioning Canada, France, and Italy in the context of refusing to agree with Britain on taking action against Turkey."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe query states that \"The Chanak Crisis is about 1922 in France,\" but the provided documents clearly indicate that the Chanak Crisis took place in 1922 and involved Turkey and Britain, not France."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The Chanak Crisis took place in Turkey (1922) and not France.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided context states the Chanak Crisis occurred in 1922 between the United Kingdom and Turkey, focusing on events in \u00c7anakkale (Chanak) on the Dardanelles Strait. There's no mention of France being directly involved as a central participant or location.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "It specifies the location as France, but all the provided context information clearly states that the Chanak Crisis took place in a city on the Anatolian side of the Dardanelles Strait, which is part of Turkey.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The Chanak Crisis took place in 1922, not in France. It involved British troops stationed in a city with importance for shipping out of the Mediterranean sea and conflicts between Turkish nationalists and Allied forces, primarily Britain and Greece, near \u00c7anakkale in Turkey.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}